Library of American Broadcasting Scripts collection
University of Maryland Libraries
- Radio and television Scripts, 1925-1991; 723 items
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/6/1936 (Folder 71.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/6/1936 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/9/1936 (Folder 72.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/9/1936 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/16/1936 (Folder 73.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/16/1936 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/23/1936 (Folder 74.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/23/1936 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/30/1936 (Folder 75.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 4/30/1936 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly -- Audition for Giddy Girl, 1/1/1937 (Folder 76.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 1/1/1937 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 3/1/1937 (Folder 77.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 3/1/1937 (Item null)
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 12/6/1937 (Folder 78.0)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 12/6/1937 (Item null)
  - First Nighter -- Carnival Dancer, 10/22/1937 (Folder 79.0)
    - First Nighter, 10/22/1937 (Item null)
  - First Nighter -- North of Hong Kong, 11/12/1937 (Folder 80.0)
    - First Nighter, 11/12/1937 (Item null)
  - First Nighter -- Broken Melody, 11/26/1937 (Folder 81.0)
    - First Nighter, 11/26/1937 (Item null)
  - First Nighter -- Opportunity Knocks, 12/3/1937 (Folder 82.0)
    - First Nighter, 12/3/1937 (Item null)
  - First Nighter -- Edgecliff Manor, 12/10/1937 (Folder 83.0)
    - First Nighter, 12/10/1937 (Item null)
  - First Nighter -- Female Companion, 12/17/1937 (Folder 84.0)
    - First Nighter, 12/17/1937 (Item null)
  - First Nighter -- Little Town of Bethlehem, 12/24/1937 (Folder 85.0)
    - First Nighter, 12/24/1937 (Item null)
  - First Nighter -- You Have to be Crazy, 2/25/1938 (Folder 86.0)
    - First Nighter, 2/25/1938 (Item null)
  - First Nighter -- The Hard Way, 7/1/1938 (Folder 87.0)
    - First Nighter, 7/1/1938 (Item null)
  - First Nighter -- Field Trial, 7/8/1938 (Folder 88.0)
    - First Nighter, 7/8/1938 (Item null)
  - First Nighter -- Understudy, 7/22/1938 (Folder 89.0)
    - First Nighter, 7/22/1938 (Item null)
  - First Nighter -- Publicity Enemy Number One, 8/26/1938 (Folder 90.0)
    - First Nighter, 8/26/1938 (Item null)
  - Five Man Report, 7/22/1952 (Folder 91.0)
    - Five Man Report, 7/22/1952 (Item null)
  - Five Man Report, 7/23/1952 (Folder 92.0)
    - Five Man Report, 7/23/1952 (Item null)
  - Flying Time with Roscoe Turner, 10/14/1937 (Folder 93.0)
    - Flying Time with Roscoe Turner, 10/14/1937 (Item null)
  - Flying Time with Roscoe Turner, 2/12/1937 (Folder 94.0)
    - Flying Time with Roscoe Turner, 2/12/1937 (Item null)
  - For Better or For Worse (Folder 95.0)
    - For Better or For Worse, null (Item null)
  - For Men Only, 1/31/1939 (Folder 96.0)
  - Ford Theater, The -- Years Ago, 10/17/1948 (Box 3, Folder 1.0)
    - Ford Theater, The, 10/17/1948 (Item null)
  - Ford Theater, The -- Joy to the World, 11/21/1948 (Folder 2.0)
    - Ford Theater, The, 11/21/1948 (Item null)
  - Ford Theater, The -- Night Must Fall, 12/19/1948 (Folder 3.0)
    - Ford Theater, The, 12/19/1948 (Item null)
  - Ford Theater, The -- The Silver Cord, 2/16/1949 (Folder 4.0)
    - Ford Theater, The, 2/16/1949 (Item null)
  - Ford Theater, The -- Outward Bound, 3/13/1949 (Folder 5.0)
    - Ford Theater, The, 3/13/1949 (Item null)
  - Ford Theater, The -- One Sunday Afternoon, 5/16/1949 (Folder 6.0)
    - Ford Theater, The, 5/16/1949 (Item null)
  - Ford Theater, The -- Light Up the Sky, 6/13/1949 (Folder 7.0)
    - Ford Theater, The, 6/13/1949 (Item null)
  - Gentlemen from Virginia, The, 2/22/1929 (Folder 8.0)
    - Gentlemen from Virginia, The, 2/22/1929 (Item null)
  - Ghosts of the Yukon (Folder 9.0)
    - Ghosts of the Yukon, null (Item null)
  - Girl Alone, 7/5/1938 (Folder 10.0)
    - Girl Alone, 7/5/1938 (Item null)
  - Girl Alone, 7/11/1938 (Folder 11.0)
    - Girl Alone, 7/11/1938 (Item null)
  - Girl Alone, 7/12/1938 (Folder 12.0)
    - Girl Alone, 7/12/1938 (Item null)
  - Girl Alone, 7/22/1938 (Folder 13.0)
    - Girl Alone, 7/22/1938 (Item null)
  - Going Through Life with Betty and Bob -- There's Trouble in the Wind, 7/11/1938 (Folder 14.0)
    - Going Through Life with Betty and Bob, 7/11/1938 (Item null)
  - Going Through Life with Betty and Bob -- There's Trouble in the Wind, 7/12/1938 (Folder 15.0)
    - Going Through Life with Betty and Bob, 7/12/1938 (Item null)
  - Going Through Life with Betty and Bob -- There's Trouble in the Wind, 7/15/1938 (Folder 16.0)
    - Going Through Life with Betty and Bob, 7/15/1938 (Item null)
  - Going Through Life with Betty and Bob -- Betty Meets Trouble Half Way Through, 7/20/1938 (Folder 17.0)
    - Going Through Life with Betty and Bob, 7/20/1938 (Item null)
  - Golf Clinic, The, 6/5/1936 (Folder 18.0)
    - Golf Clinic, The, 6/5/1936 (Item null)
  - Good Friday Broadcast, 4/19/1947 (Folder 19.0)
    - Good Friday Broadcast, 4/19/1947 (Item null)
  - Grace Wilson, 11/11/1946 (Folder 20.0)
    - Grace Wilson, 11/11/1946 (Item null)
  - Grand Slam, 9/30/1947 (Folder 21.0)
    - Grand Slam, 9/30/1947 (Item null)
  - Grand Slam, 9/30/1949 (Folder 22.0)
    - Grand Slam, 9/30/1949 (Item null)
  - Great Gildersleeve, The, 8/30/1942 (Folder 23.0)
    - Great Gildersleeve, The, 8/30/1942 (Item null)
  - Guiding Light, The, 7/5/1938 (Folder 24.0)
    - Guiding Light, The, 7/5/1938 (Item null)
  - Guiding Light, The, 7/7/1938 (Folder 25.0)
    - Guiding Light, The, 7/7/1938 (Item null)
  - Guiding Light, The -- Juggler of Our Lady, 7/11/1938 (Folder 26.0)
  - Gulf Screen Guild Theatre, 12/31/1941 (Folder 27.0)
    - Gulf Screen Guild Theatre, 12/31/1941 (Item null)
  - Hail and Farewell, 11/2/1946 (Folder 28.0)
    - Hail and Farewell, 11/2/1946 (Item null)
  - Handy Andy: A Sound Slidefilm, 3/25/1949 (Folder 29.0)
    - Handy Andy: A Sound Slidefilm, 3/25/1949 (Item null)
  - Hap Hazard, 7/15/1941 (Folder 30.0)
    - Hap Hazard, 7/15/1941 (Item null)
  - Hap Hazard, 7/22/1941 (Folder 31.0)
    - Hap Hazard, 7/22/1941 (Item null)
  - Hap Hazard -- miscellaneous, 8/5/1941 (Folder 32.0)
    - Hap Hazard, 8/5/1941 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- The Fifth Wheel (Folder 33.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, null (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Report from the World, 1/4/1947 (Folder 34.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 1/4/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- The Marriage Gallery, 1/11/1947 (Folder 35.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 1/11/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- The Inner Voices, 1/18/1947 (Folder 36.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 1/18/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Stop That Nonesense, 2/1/1947 (Folder 37.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 2/1/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Home is Really What You Make It, 2/8/1947 (Folder 38.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 2/8/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Your Haunted House, 2/15/1947 (Folder 39.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 2/15/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Alcoholism - Sin or Sickness, 3/8/1947 (Folder 40.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 3/8/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Take A Look At Yourself, 3/15/1947 (Folder 41.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 3/15/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Out on a Limb, 3/29/1947 (Folder 42.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 3/29/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Between Friends, 4/5/1947 (Folder 43.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 4/5/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Talents and Children, 4/12/1947 (Folder 44.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 4/12/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- The Case of the Coiled Spring, 4/26/1947 (Folder 45.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 4/26/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Carrie Chapman Catt: Mother of the Rights of Women, 5/3/1947 (Folder 46.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 5/3/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Story Without Accents, 5/10/1947 (Folder 47.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 5/10/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Hans Christian Andersen.. The Ugly Duckling Who C, 5/17/1947 (Folder 48.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 5/17/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- China -- A Sculptor of American History, 5/31/1947 (Folder 49.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 5/31/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- South Africa -- Diamond Mine to America, 6/7/1947 (Folder 50.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 6/7/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- The West Indes.. From Columbus to Cane, Cotton a, 6/14/1947 (Folder 51.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 6/14/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- A Russian Design for Laughter - The Inspector Gene, 6/21/1947 (Folder 52.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 6/21/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- A Tribute to Mother England, 6/28/1947 (Folder 53.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 6/28/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Aesop -- Fables for Today and Tommorrow, 7/5/1947 (Folder 54.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 7/5/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Paderewski -- Pianist and Patriotic, 7/12/1947 (Folder 55.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 7/12/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Leeuwenhoek -- The Man Who Gave US Magic Eyes, 7/19/1947 (Folder 56.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 7/19/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Siam -- Our Collaborator in Victory, 7/26/1947 (Folder 57.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 7/26/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Cornfed America - A Mexican Heritage, 8/14/1947 (Folder 58.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 8/14/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Alfred Nobel... From Dynamite to Peace, 8/23/1947 (Folder 59.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 8/23/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Puerto Rico -- American Island, 8/30/1947 (Folder 60.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 8/30/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Here's To Youth, 9/6/1947 (Folder 61.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 9/6/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- School Daze, 9/20/1947 (Folder 62.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 9/20/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Love in Bloom, 10/4/1947 (Folder 63.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 10/4/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Early to Bed, 10/11/1947 (Folder 64.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 10/11/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Puppets and Purse-Strings, 10/18/1947 (Folder 65.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 10/18/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Freedom is a Home-Made Thing, 10/25/1947 (Folder 66.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 10/25/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- The Little Dictator, 11/1/1947 (Folder 67.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 11/1/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Dear Benefactor, 11/8/1947 (Folder 68.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 11/8/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Santa Claus Will Get You If You Don't Watch Out, 11/22/1947 (Folder 69.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 11/22/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It -- Atomic Energy Is Your Business, 11/29/1947 (Folder 70.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 11/29/1947 (Item null)
  - Home Is What You Make It, 11/17/1948 (Folder 71.0)
    - Home Is What You Make It, 11/17/1948 (Item null)
  - How to Know People, 7/3/1944 (Folder 72.0)
    - How to Know People, 7/3/1944 (Item null)
  - How to Play Baseball, 10/25/1943 (Folder 73.0)
    - How to Play Baseball, 10/25/1943 (Item null)
  - Hymns of All Churches -- The Tropics Don't Call It Murder, 7/14/1938 (Folder 74.0)
    - Hymns of All Churches, 7/14/1938 (Item null)
  - I Love a Mystery -- The Tropics Don't Call It Murder, 2/23/1950 (Folder 75.0)
    - I Love a Mystery, 2/23/1950 (Item null)
  - I Love a Mystery, 2/24/1950 (Folder 76.0)
    - I Love a Mystery, 2/24/1950 (Item null)
  - Illinois versus Stanford Universtiy, 10/3/1953 (Folder 77.0)
    - Illinois versus Stanford Universtiy, 10/3/1953 (Item null)
  - Initiation of Climbing Eels, 1/3/1925 (Folder 78.0)
    - Initiation of Climbing Eels, 1/3/1925 (Item null)
  - Interesting Neighbors, 7/3/1938 (Folder 79.0)
    - Interesting Neighbors, 7/3/1938 (Item null)
  - Interesting Neighbors -- The Red Shoes, 7/10/1938 (Folder 80.0)
    - Interesting Neighbors, 7/10/1938 (Item null)
  - Ireene Wicker - The Singing Lady -- A Christmas Carol, 11/6/1949 (Folder 81.0)
    - Ireene Wicker - The Singing Lady, 11/6/1949 (Item null)
  - Ireene Wicker - The Singing Lady -- Snow White and Rose Red, 12/18/1949 (Folder 82.0)
    - Ireene Wicker - The Singing Lady, 12/18/1949 (Item null)
  - Ireene Wicker - The Singing Lady -- The Nutcracker, 3/19/1950 (Folder 83.0)
    - Ireene Wicker - The Singing Lady, 3/19/1950 (Item null)
  - Ireene Wicker Show, The, 12/26/1948 (Folder 84.0)
    - Ireene Wicker Show, The, 12/26/1948 (Item null)
  - Jean Valjean and the Bishop (Folder 85.0)
    - Jean Valjean and the Bishop, null (Item null)
  - Jo and Vi -- Hooked (Folder 86.0)
    - Jo and Vi, null (Item null)
  - Jo and Vi -- Vitamin H, 9/21/1929 (Folder 87.0)
    - Jo and Vi, 9/21/1929 (Item null)
  - Jo and Vi -- The Culture Club, 9/28/1929 (Folder 88.0)
    - Jo and Vi, 9/28/1929 (Item null)
  - Jo and Vi -- Thanksgiving Masquerade, 11/16/1929 (Box 4, Folder 1.0)
    - Jo and Vi, 11/23/1929 (Item null)
  - Jo and Vi -- A Manual for Moochers, 11/23/1929 (Folder 2.0)
    - Jo and Vi, 2/18/1930 (Item null)
  - Jo and Vi -- Man's Best Friend, 2/18/1930 (Folder 3.0)
    - Jo and Vi, 3/4/1930 (Item null)
  - Jo and Vi -- In the Spring A Young Man's Fancy, 3/4/1930 (Folder 4.0)
    - Jo and Vi, 3/18/1930 (Item null)
  - Jo and Vi -- Going Up, 3/18/1930 (Folder 5.0)
    - Jo and Vi, 3/25/1930 (Item null)
  - Jo and Vi -- Help! Help!, 3/25/1930 (Folder 6.0)
    - Jo and Vi, 4/14/1931 (Item null)
  - Jo and Vi -- Neighbor Joe, 4/14/1931 (Folder 7.0)
    - Jo and Vi, 4/21/1931 (Item null)
  - Jo and Vi -- Cooked, 4/21/1931 (Folder 8.0)
    - Jo and Vi, 5/5/1931 (Item null)
  - Jo and Vi, 5/5/1931 (Folder 9.0)
    - Josh Higgins, 7/22/1938 (Item null)
  - Josh Higgins, 7/22/1938 (Folder 10.0)
    - Just Neighbors, 7/5/1938 (Item null)
  - Just Neighbors, 7/5/1938 (Folder 11.0)
    - Just Neighbors, 7/11/1938 (Item null)
  - Just Neighbors, 7/11/1938 (Folder 12.0)
    - Just Neighbors, 7/15/1938 (Item null)
  - Just Neighbors, 7/15/1938 (Folder 13.0)
    - Just Neighbors, 7/21/1938 (Item null)
  - Just Neighbors, 7/21/1938 (Folder 14.0)
    - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 11/12/1937 (Item null)
  - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 11/12/1937 (Folder 15.0)
    - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 7/2/1938 (Item null)
  - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 7/2/1938 (Folder 16.0)
    - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 7/9/1938 (Item null)
  - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 7/9/1938 (Folder 17.0)
    - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 8/6/1938 (Item null)
  - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 8/6/1938 (Folder 18.0)
    - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 8/17/1938 (Item null)
  - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 8/17/1938 (Folder 19.0)
    - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 8/20/1938 (Item null)
  - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 8/20/1938 (Folder 20.0)
    - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 8/27/1938 (Item null)
  - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 8/27/1938 (Folder 21.0)
    - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 9/3/1938 (Item null)
  - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 9/3/1938 (Folder 22.0)
    - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 9/10/1938 (Item null)
  - Kaltenmeyer's Kindergarten, 9/10/1938 (Folder 23.0)
    - Kate Smith Hour, The, 11/25/1944 (Item null)
  - Kate Smith Hour, The, 11/25/1944 (Folder 24.0)
    - King Arthur's Court, 10/27/1943 (Item null)
  - King Arthur's Court, 10/27/1943 (Folder 25.0)
    - King Arthur's Court, 11/24/1943 (Item null)
  - King Arthur's Court, 11/24/1943 (Folder 26.0)
    - King Arthur's Court, 12/1/1943 (Item null)
  - King Arthur's Court -- The Search Gwen Owen, 12/1/1943 (Folder 27.0)
    - Kitty Keene, Inc, 7/11/1938 (Item null)
  - Kitty Keene, Inc, 7/11/1938 (Folder 28.0)
    - Korn Krib, 11/9/1946 (Item null)
  - Korn Krib, 11/9/1946 (Folder 29.0)
    - Korn Krib, 11/23/1946 (Item null)
  - Korn Krib, 11/23/1946 (Folder 30.0)
    - Lady Esther Serenade, The, 7/5/1938 (Item null)
  - Lady Esther Serenade, The, 7/5/1938 (Folder 31.0)
    - Last of the Lockwoods, The, 1/9/1938 (Item null)
  - Last of the Lockwoods, The, 1/9/1938 (Folder 32.0)
    - Last of the Lockwoods, The, 1/16/1938 (Item null)
  - Last of the Lockwoods, The, 1/16/1938 (Folder 33.0)
    - Last of the Lockwoods, The, 2/13/1938 (Item null)
  - Last of the Lockwoods, The, 2/13/1938 (Folder 34.0)
    - Leif Eid Reports on Inflation, 11/1/1948 (Item null)
  - Leif Eid Reports on Inflation, 11/1/1948 (Folder 35.0)
    - Let Freedom Sing, 6/1/1942 (Item null)
  - Let Freedom Sing, 6/1/1942 (Folder 36.0)
    - Let's Spend Some Time Together, 3/1/1946 (Item null)
  - Let's Spend Some Time Together, 3/1/1946 (Folder 37.0)
    - Let's Spend Some Time Together, 4/6/1946 (Item null)
  - Let's Spend Some Time Together, 4/6/1946 (Folder 38.0)
    - Lights Out, 10/23/1935 (Item null)
  - Lights Out, 10/23/1935 (Folder 39.0)
    - Lights Out, 12/4/1935 (Item null)
  - Lights Out -- The Dark, 12/4/1935 (Folder 40.0)
    - Lights Out, 1/19/1938 (Item null)
  - Lights Out -- Gevangenpoort, 1/19/1938 (Folder 41.0)
    - Lights Out, 7/6/1938 (Item null)
  - Lights Out -- The Hounds of Weir, 7/6/1938 (Folder 42.0)
    - Lights Out, 7/20/1938 (Item null)
  - Lights Out, 7/20/1938 (Folder 43.0)
    - Literary Camoes, 2/25/1929 (Item null)
  - Literary Camoes -- The Red Shoes, 2/25/1929 (Folder 44.0)
    - Little Lady Story Time Starring Ireene Wicker, 10/11/1953 (Item null)
  - Little Lady Story Time Starring Ireene Wicker -- Adventures in China, 10/11/1953 (Folder 45.0)
    - Little Orphan Annie, 7/5/1938 (Item null)
  - Little Orphan Annie -- Adventures in China, 7/5/1938 (Folder 46.0)
    - Little Orphan Annie, 7/7/1938 (Item null)
  - Little Orphan Annie -- Adventures in China, 7/7/1938 (Folder 47.0)
    - Little Orphan Annie, 7/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Little Orphan Annie -- Adventures in China, 7/8/1938 (Folder 48.0)
    - Little Orphan Annie, 7/21/1938 (Item null)
  - Little Orphan Annie -- The Case of the Pine Ridge Firebug, 7/21/1938 (Folder 49.0)
    - Lum and Abner, 1/2/1936 (Item null)
  - Lum and Abner, 1/2/1936 (Folder 50.0)
    - Ma Perkins, 7/4/1938 (Item null)
  - Ma Perkins, 7/4/1938 (Folder 51.0)
    - Ma Perkins, 7/11/1938 (Item null)
  - Ma Perkins, 7/11/1938 (Folder 52.0)
    - Ma Perkins, 7/15/1938 (Item null)
  - Ma Perkins, 7/15/1938 (Folder 53.0)
    - Ma Perkins, 7/21/1938 (Item null)
  - Ma Perkins -- Seven Were Saved, 7/21/1938 (Folder 54.0)
    - Mages Sunday Playhouse, 3/25/1959 (Item null)
  - Mages Sunday Playhouse, 3/25/1959 (Folder 55.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 4/24/1946 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 4/24/1946 (Folder 56.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 10/2/1946 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 10/2/1946 (Folder 57.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 10/9/1946 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 10/9/1946 (Folder 58.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 10/16/1946 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 10/16/1946 (Folder 59.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 10/30/1946 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 10/30/1946 (Folder 60.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 11/6/1946 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 11/6/1946 (Folder 61.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 11/13/1946 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 11/13/1946 (Folder 62.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 11/27/1946 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 11/27/1946 (Folder 63.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 11/30/1946 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 11/30/1946 (Folder 64.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 1/15/1947 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 1/15/1947 (Folder 65.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 1/22/1947 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 1/22/1947 (Folder 66.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 1/29/1947 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 1/29/1947 (Folder 67.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 2/5/1947 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 2/5/1947 (Folder 68.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 2/12/1947 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 2/12/1947 (Folder 69.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 2/19/1947 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 2/19/1947 (Folder 70.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 2/26/1947 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 2/26/1947 (Folder 71.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 3/5/1947 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 3/5/1947 (Folder 72.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 3/12/1947 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 3/12/1947 (Folder 73.0)
    - Magic Harp, The, 4/2/1947 (Item null)
  - Magic Harp, The, 4/2/1947 (Folder 74.0)
    - Magic of Broadcasting, The, null (Item null)
  - Magic of Broadcasting, The (Folder 75.0)
    - Maltex Broadcast - New York City, 12/17/1933 (Item null)
  - Maltex Broadcast - New York City, 12/17/1933 (Folder 76.0)
    - Maltex Program, 9/30/1934 (Item null)
  - Maltex Program, 9/30/1934 (Folder 77.0)
    - Mary and Bob's True Stories, 2/21/1939 (Item null)
  - Mary and Bob's True Stories, 2/21/1939 (Folder 78.0)
    - Mary Marlin, 7/6/1938 (Item null)
  - Mary Marlin -- (commercial only), 7/6/1938 (Folder 79.0)
    - Mary Marlin, 7/7/1938 (Item null)
  - Mary Marlin, 7/7/1938 (Folder 80.0)
    - Mary Marlin, 7/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Mary Marlin, 7/8/1938 (Folder 81.0)
    - Mary Marlin, 7/12/1938 (Item null)
  - Mary Marlin, 7/12/1938 (Folder 82.0)
    - Mary Marlin, 7/22/1938 (Item null)
  - Mary Marlin -- Law Goes to Cottonwood, 7/22/1938 (Folder 83.0)
    - Meadow Gold Round Up, 7/28/1938 (Item null)
  - Meadow Gold Round Up, 7/28/1938 (Folder 84.0)
    - Meet the Press, 1/27/1970 (Item null)
  - Meet the Press -- Lest We Forget, 1/27/1970 (Folder 85.0)
    - Memorial Day Feature, 5/21/1956 (Item null)
  - Memorial Day Feature -- War of the Worlds, 5/21/1956 (Folder 86.0)
    - Mercury Theater of the Air, 10/30/1938 (Item null)
  - Mercury Theater of the Air, 10/30/1938 (Folder 87.0)
    - Money Talks, 8/20/1962 (Item null)
  - Money Talks, 8/20/1962 (Folder 88.0)
    - Morris B. Sachs Amateur Hour, 7/10/1938 (Item null)
  - Morris B. Sachs Amateur Hour -- miscellaneous, 7/10/1938 (Folder 89.0)
    - Jo and Vi, 11/16/1929 (Item null)
    - Mr. and Mrs., null (Item null)
  - Mr. and Mrs. -- The Perfect Alabi (Folder 90.0)
    - Mr. and Mrs., 5/22/1930 (Item null)
  - Mr. and Mrs., 5/22/1930 (Folder 91.0)
    - Mr. and Mrs., 5/28/1930 (Item null)
  - Mr. and Mrs. -- Rent Free, 5/28/1930 (Folder 92.0)
    - Mr. and Mrs., 6/10/1930 (Item null)
  - Mr. and Mrs. -- Farmer Joe, 6/10/1930 (Folder 93.0)
    - Mr. and Mrs., 6/17/1930 (Item null)
  - Mr. and Mrs. -- Swamped, 6/17/1930 (Folder 94.0)
    - Mr. and Mrs., 7/1/1930 (Item null)
  - Mr. and Mrs. -- By-Products, 7/1/1930 (Folder 95.0)
    - Mr. and Mrs., 7/8/1930 (Item null)
  - Mr. and Mrs. -- Its An Old Swedish Custom, 7/8/1930 (Folder 96.0)
    - Mr. and Mrs., 8/12/1930 (Item null)
  - Mr. and Mrs. -- The Hardy Perennial, 8/12/1930 (Folder 97.0)
    - Mr. and Mrs., 12/16/1930 (Item null)
  - Mr. and Mrs., 12/16/1930 (Folder 98.0)
    - Nate Gross' Town Tattler, 10/8/1944 (Item null)
  - Nate Gross' Town Tattler -- The Hayloft Minstrels, 10/8/1944 (Folder 99.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 2/1/1947 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 2/1/1947 (Folder 100.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 7/3/1948 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 7/3/1948 (Folder 101.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 7/10/1948 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 7/10/1948 (Folder 102.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 7/24/1948 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 7/24/1948 (Folder 103.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 7/31/1948 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 7/31/1948 (Folder 104.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 9/11/1948 (Item null)